<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Drug Recovery App</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_acc">ViewAccActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="i_am_fully_qualified_integrative_therapist_working_with_children_adolescents_and_adults_exploring_emotional_histories_life_experiences_gaining_better_awareness_of_self_navigating_testing_times_are_some_of_the_reasons_why_people_seek_therapy">I am fully qualified Integrative Therapist working with children, adolescents and adults. Exploring emotional histories, life experiences, gaining better awareness of self, navigating testing times are some of the reasons why people seek therapy.</string>
    <string name="chat_with_me">Chat With Me</string>
    <string name="about_me">About Me</string>
    <string name="mbacp_pgdip_pgcert_semh_spc_ba_hons_qts">MBACP, PGDip, PGCert, SEMH Spc, BA HONS (QTS)</string>
    <string name="counsellor_samia">Counsellor Samia</string>
    <string name="chat_with_me1">Chat With Me</string>
    <string name="i_am_a_psychotherapist_and_counsellor_offering_a_warm_supportive_confidential_service_for_individuals_each_person_responds_to_the_events_that_happen_in_their_lives_differently_your_issue_what_you_would_like_to_bring_to_therapy_is_the_starting_point_for_our_work_together">I am a psychotherapist and counsellor offering a warm, supportive confidential service for individuals. Each person responds to the events that happen in their lives differently. Your issue, what you would like to bring to therapy is the starting point for our work together.</string>
    <string name="about_me1">About Me</string>
    <string name="counsellor_judith">Counsellor Judith</string>
    <string name="ukcp_msc_psychotherapy_and_counselling_bacp_mupca">UKCP, Msc Psychotherapy and Counselling, BACP, MUPCA</string>
    <string name="create_posts">Create Posts</string>
    <string name="chat_rooms">Chat Rooms</string>
    <string name="discussion_groups">Discussion Groups</string>
    <string name="search_friend">Search Friend</string>
    <string name="menu_page">Menu Page</string>
    <string name="community_forum">Community Forum</string>
    <string name="discussion_group">Discussion Groups</string>
    <string name="chat_room">Chat Rooms</string>
    <string name="counsellor_contact">Counsellor Contacts</string>
    <string name="search_for_friends">Search for Friends</string>
    <string name="community_forums">Community Forum</string>
    <string name="create_posts_btn">Create Posts</string>
    <string name="popular_posts">Popular Posts</string>
    <string name="counsellor_contacts">Counsellor Contacts</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_practical10">Practical10</string>
    <string name="tittle_SuccessStory1">From Darkness to Light:</string>
    <string name="description_SuccessStory1">My Personal Journey of Drug Abuse Recovery</string>
    <string name="title_SuccessStory2">Breaking the Chains:</string>
    <string name="description_SuccessStory2"> A Personal Odyssey of Redemption
</string>
    <string name="title_SuccessStory3">From Desolation to Liberation:</string>
    <string name="description_SuccessStory3">My Triumph Over Addiction</string>
    <string name="story1">In the heart of my struggles, where the shadows of addiction loomed large, I embarked on a journey that would redefine my existence. This is the story of my recovery, a testament to the strength within and the unwavering support that guided me from darkness to light.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"The beginning was marked by a realization—an epiphany that cut through the haze of substance abuse. It was a stark acknowledgment that the path I treaded was leading to self-destruction. The whispers of my loved ones and the pain in their eyes became the catalyst for change.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"With newfound determination, I sought solace in the arms of those who cared. Friends and family, once distant in the chaos of addiction, became the pillars of my support system. Their love was the lifeline that pulled me from the depths of despair, and together, we vowed to face the challenges that lay ahead.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Embracing recovery meant confronting the demons within, understanding the roots of my addiction, and unraveling the layers that shrouded my true self. Therapy sessions, both individual and group, became my sanctuary, providing a space to explore the pain and fears that fueled my substance abuse.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Rehabilitation became my refuge—a place of healing and rediscovery. It was within these walls that I learned to replace destructive habits with positive ones, forging new connections with art, music, and physical activities. Each day was a step forward, a triumph over the struggles that threatened to pull me back.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"The journey was far from linear, marked by relapses and moments of doubt. Yet, with unwavering perseverance, I celebrated the small victories—days of sobriety turning into weeks, and weeks into months. The path was arduous, but with each setback, I found the strength to rise again.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"As the chapters of my recovery unfolded, I discovered a profound sense of purpose. No longer defined by the chains of addiction, I became a beacon of hope for others still navigating the shadows. My story, once etched in pain, transformed into a narrative of resilience, inspiring those who faced similar struggles.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Today, as I look back at the town that witnessed my journey, its streets echo not only with tales of despair but also with the resounding success of my recovery. My story is not just mine—it is a shared testament to the indomitable spirit that can emerge from the depths of addiction.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"In sharing my experience, I hope to illuminate the path for others seeking recovery. From the darkness of addiction to the light of sobriety, this is a story of personal triumph—a reminder that within every struggle, the potential for transformation exists, and recovery is not just a destination but a continuous journey towards self-discovery and healing.
</string>
    <string name="story2">In the labyrinth of addiction, I found myself entangled in a web of self-destruction. The allure of substances promised an escape, a fleeting reprieve from the harsh realities of life. Little did I know that this escape would soon morph into a relentless nightmare, consuming every facet of my existence.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"The realization that I had become a prisoner of my own vices hit me like a thunderbolt. The relationships I cherished crumbled, dreams withered away, and the vibrant colors of life faded into a monochromatic existence dictated by the next fix. Rock bottom became the solid foundation on which I decided to rebuild my life.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"The journey to recovery was riddled with moments of anguish, but each step forward was a defiance against the chains that bound me. Rehabilitation became my sanctuary—a place where the echoes of despair were drowned out by the hopeful whispers of redemption. Therapy sessions peeled back the layers of trauma, unveiling the wounds that fueled my descent into addiction.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Support from loved ones became the backbone of my recovery. Their unwavering belief in my ability to overcome echoed louder than the doubts that lingered within. Together, we navigated the tumultuous seas of rehabilitation, finding solace in the shared goal of reclaiming a life lost to substances.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Sobriety, once an abstract concept, became a tangible reality. With each sober day, I rediscovered the beauty of a sunrise, the warmth of genuine laughter, and the profound connections that define the human experience. The journey was not without its challenges; relapses cast shadows on the path, but they were mere detours, not roadblocks.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Recovery became synonymous with rediscovery. Hobbies long forgotten were rekindled, and passions once extinguished roared back to life. Sobriety was not just abstinence—it was a process of rebuilding, of forging a new identity from the ashes of the old.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Today, as I stand on the shores of redemption, I am not defined by the scars of my past. They serve as reminders of battles fought and resilience unearthed. The person I am today is a testament to the transformative power of choosing recovery, of embracing the journey with all its twists and turns.

    </string>
    <string name="story3">In the depths of despair, where shadows clung to every corner of my existence, I stood at the crossroads between surrender and resilience. Substance abuse had woven its insidious tendrils into the fabric of my life, ensnaring me in a cycle of self-destruction. The abyss seemed bottomless, but within its darkness, I discovered a glimmer of hope—a seed of determination that would sprout into my salvation.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"The journey to sobriety was not a linear ascent; rather, it resembled a mountain range, with peaks of progress and valleys of setbacks. The road to recovery demanded a courage I never knew I possessed and an unwavering commitment to face the demons that had long haunted me.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Rehabilitation became my sanctuary, a cocoon where metamorphosis unfolded. Group therapy sessions provided a mirror to my soul, reflecting the pain and trauma that had fueled my descent. In the shared stories of fellow warriors, I found solace—a reminder that I was not alone in my struggle.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Support from loved ones became the cornerstone of my recovery. Their encouragement was a lifeline in moments of weakness, and their love became the compass guiding me through the labyrinth of rehabilitation. Together, we rewrote the narrative of my life, erasing the chapters stained by addiction and authoring a story of resilience and renewal.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Sobriety, once an elusive dream, manifested as a daily triumph over cravings and triggers. Each sunrise became a symbol of renewal, a promise that the darkest nights could not extinguish the light within. The relapses, while disheartening, were not the end of the road but rather detours that redirected me toward a steadfast commitment to recovery.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Reclaiming my identity from the clutches of addiction was a process of self-discovery. Hobbies and passions, once obscured by the haze of substances, regained their vibrancy. As I embraced a sober existence, I uncovered the intricacies of my true self—a self that had been buried beneath the numbing effects of addiction.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"Today, as a testament to the resilience of the human spirit, I stand on the summit of sobriety. The scars of my past are not blemishes but rather markers of battles won. My triumph over addiction is not just a personal victory; it is a beacon of hope for those navigating the labyrinth of despair.
        "\n\n\t\t\t"To those still entangled in the clutches of addiction, my story is a testament that recovery is not an unattainable mirage but a tangible destination. With courage, perseverance, and a support system, the journey from desolation to liberation is possible, and the dawn of a new, sober life awaits those who dare to embark on the path of healing.
</string>
</resources>